Guide to the Andover Theological Seminary Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Publications, Series X
  - Catalogs (unbound)
    - Annual/general catalogs, 1890–1901 (Box 39)
    - Annual/general catalogs, 1901–1911 (Box 40)
    - Annual/general catalogs, 1911–1922 (Box 41)
    - Annual/general catalogs, 1922–1927 (Box 42)
    - Theological Seminary Bulletin, 1889 (Box 72)
    - Triennial catalogs, 1839–1845 (Box 42)
    - Triennial catalogs, 1848–1867 (Box 43)
    - Triennial catalogs, 1870 (Box 44)
    - Triennial catalogs: notations, 1870 (Box 68)
  - Programs
    - Commencement programs, 1818–1886 (Box 71)
    - Commencement programs, 1818–1949 (Box 69, Folder 1-16)
    - Commencement programs, 1887–1922 (Box 70, Folder 9-12)
    - Commencement programs, 1950–1965 (Box 70, Folder 1-8)
    - Sermons and addresses, 1808–1883 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Titles
    - Act of Incorporation of Phillips Academy in Andover [Massachusetts], c.1780 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Andover Review: A Religious and Theological Monthly (volumes 1-19), 1884–1893 (Box 73–75)
    - Andover Review Company: corporate records, 1883-1893, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 13-16)
    - Andover Theological Documents (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Creed of Andover Theological Seminary, 1882, 1887 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Dates and Data, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Description of the Theological Institution at Andover [Massachusetts], 1834 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Exercises Commemorating the Two-Hundredth Anniversary of the Birth of Jonathan Edwards Held at Andover Theological Seminary October 4 and 5, 1903, 1904 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - History of Andover Theological Seminary, 1933 (Box 179)
    - History of the Andover Theological Seminary, 1885 (Box 179)
    - Memorial of the Semi-Centennial Celebration at the Founding of the Theological Seminary at Andover [Massachusetts], 1859 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Old New England School: A History of Phillips Academy, Andover [Mass.], 1917 (Box 179)
    - Reminiscences of Andover Newton, 1914 (Box 179)
    - Sermon in Commemoration of William Bartlet, Esquire, an Associate Founder of the Theological Seminary in Andover [Massachusetts], 1814 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Sermon Occasioned by the Completion of the New College Edifice the Use of the Theological Seminary at Andover [Massachusetts], 1821 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Subscription to the Andover Seminary Creed required by the Decision of the Supreme Judicial Court for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, 1927 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Theological Bibliographies [copies #1-2], 1963 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
- Related Organizations, Series XI
  - Andover Seminary Church
    - Account book, 1872–1932 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Bible, 1862 (Box 155)
    - Correspondence, 1816–1931 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Creed and Covenant, 1867, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Deposit book, 1911–1931 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Historical documents, 1816, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Hymn book, 1873 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Membership records, 1869-1928, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1865 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Other papers, 1876-1908, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Record book, 1865–1930 (Box 155)
    - Worship books, 1891 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Other related organizations
    - Committee to Revise Bible, Oriental Schools: proofs, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 1-7)
    - Female Mite Society: Constitution and minutes, 1822–1881 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Revival Association: records, 1832–1833 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Samaritan Female Society
    - Account book, 1817–1931 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Constitution, 1818–1915 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Constitution and minutes, 1817–1919 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1875-1940, n.d. (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Financial records, 1880–1992 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 1854-1924, n.d. (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 1921–1924 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Reports: Treasurer, 1904–1918 (Box 151, Folder 18)